Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Artists Files
  - Sugarman, George #2, undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Sugarman, George #3, undated (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Sugimoto, Hiroshi - Photos/Slides, 1978-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Sugimoto, Hiroshi - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Suh, Do-Ho - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Suh, Do-Ho - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sultan, Donald - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1989-2003 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sultan, Donald - Photos/Slides, 1989-1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sultan, David - Reviews, 1986-1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Surls, James - Photos/Slides, 1983-1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Surls, James - Reviews, 1980-1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Surls, James - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1984-1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Surls, James, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Sze, Sarah - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sze, Sarah - Photos/Slides, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Sze, Sarah - Reviews, 1996-1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Taho, Ritsuko, 1985-1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Taho, Ritsuko - Reviews, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Taho, Ritsuko - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1988-1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Taho, Ritsuko - Photos/Slides, 1986-1995 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Takaezu, Toshinko - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997-2006 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Takaezu, Toshinko - Photos/Slides, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Takaezu, Toshinko - Reviews, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Taniguchi, Gaha - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Taniguchi, Gaha - Photos/Slides, 1985-1994 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Taniguchi, Gaha - Reviews, 1987-1992 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Tansey, Mark, 1982-1996 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Tansey, Mark, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Tape Art - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Tape Art - Photos/Slides: Cultural Connection Murals, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Tape Art - Photos/Slides: Carondelet 13, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Taper, Geri, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Tapies, Antoni, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Taradash, Meryl - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Taradash, Meryl - Reviews, 1988-1999 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Taradash, Meryl - Photos/Slides, 1992-2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Tasende, Jose, 1990-2002 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Tawney, Lenore - Photos/Slides, 1957-1999 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Tawney, Lenore - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1983-1996 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Tawney, Lenore - Reviews, 1986-1993 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Tawney, Lenore, 1965-1984 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Taylor-Wood, Sam - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Tegeder, Dannielle - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Teicher, Lois - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994-2002 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Teicher, Lois - Photos/Slides, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Telleria, Marisa - Photos/Slides, 1998-2003 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Telleria-Diez, Marisa - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Teruya, Yuken - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Teruya, Yuken - Photos/Slides, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Teruya, Yuken - Reviews, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Teshigahara, Hiroshi - Reviews, undated (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Testa, Clorindo, 1977-1986 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Tevereterno, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Thater, Diana- Invitation, Bio, Exhibition Info, 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Thater, Diana-Photos/Slides, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Therrien, Robert, May 1987 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Therrien, Robert-Photos/Slides, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Therrien, Robert- Reviews, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Therrien, Robert- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 1995, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Thomasos, Denyse- Photos/Slides, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Tillers, Imants- Photos/Slides, 1985-1990 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Tillers, Imants- Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Tillers, Imants- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Tinguely, Jean- Photos, Bio, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Tinguely, Jean, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Tinguely, Jean- Invitations, Bio, Exhibition Info, 1978-1998 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Tinguely, Jean- Slides, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Tolle, Brian, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Tolle, Brian- Presentation: Irish Hungar Memorial, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Tolle, Brian-Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Tolle, Brian- Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Tolle, Brian- Reviews, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Tomaselli, Fred- Reviews, 1990-1993 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Tomaselli, Fred- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 1992-1998 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Tomaselli, Fred- Photos/Slides, 1992-1994 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Topolski, Andy- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Topolski, Andy- Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Topolski, Andy- Proposals, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Trakas, George- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Trakas, George- Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Trakas, George- Photos, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Trakas, George- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Trockel, Rosmarie, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Trockel, Rosmarie-Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 1988-2004 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Trombly, Frances-Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Tsai, F., [undated] (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Tsou Fong, Betty, 1983-1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Tucker, William, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Tucker, William- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Tucker, William-Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Tucker, William- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Tucker, William- Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Tunick, Susan- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Tunick, Susan- Slides, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Tunick, Susan- Slides/Photos, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Tunick, Susan- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Turkle, Tyler, 1981-1989 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Turner, Judith- Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Turrel, James- Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Turrel, James- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Turrel, James- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Turrel, James- Slides, 1967-1975 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Tuttle, Richard, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Tuttle, Richard-Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Tuymans, Luc- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit info, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Ukeles, Mierle- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit, Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Ukeles, Mierle- Photos/Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Ukeles, Mierle- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Ungers, Simon, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Uprutchard, Francis- Invitations, Bio, Exhibi Info, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Ulse, Juan- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit, Info, 1994, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Ulse, Juan- Reviews, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Van Alstine, John, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Vaisman, Meyer, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Vari, Sophia- Slides, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Varini, Felice- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Varini, Felice- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Varini, Felice- Photos/Slides, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Veca, Mark Dean, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Venet, Burnar, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Venet, Burnar- Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Venet, Burnar- Slides/Photos, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Venet, Burnar- Reviews, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Venet, Burnar- Slides, [undated] (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Venet, Burnar- Slides, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Villareal, Leo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2002 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Villareal, Leo - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Vilmount, Jean-Luc - Reviews, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Viola, Bill - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Von Bonin, Cosima - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Von Bonin, Cosima - Reviews, 1991-2003 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Von Gal, Edwina - Reviews, undated (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Von Gal, Edwina - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Von Gal, Edwina - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Reviews, undated (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Proposals, undated (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula, undated (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula, undated (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Von Schlegell, David - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Von Schlegell, David, undated (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Von Schlegell, David #2, undated (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Von Schlegell, David #3, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Von Schlegell, David, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Waisman, Karin - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Waisman, Karin - Reviews, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Wall, Jeff - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Wall, Jeff - Photos/Slides, 1980, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Wall, Jeff - Reviews, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Wanas Foundation - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1997 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ward, Nari - Reviews, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Warek Meister, Laura, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Watkins, Tim, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Watkins, Tim, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Wakabayashi, Isamu, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Watz, Kevin - Reviews, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Webster, Meg - Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Webster, Meg - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Webster, Meg - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Webster, Meg - Reviews, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Wegman, William - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2006 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Wegner, Peter - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Weinberg, Ed - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Weinberg, Ed - Reviews, undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Weiner, Lawrence - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Weiner, Lawrence - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Wells, David, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Wells, David, undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Welz, Rebecca, undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Wentworth, undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Werblud, Derba - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Wesselman, Tom, undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - West, Franz, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - West, Franz - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Westerlund, Roosen M., undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Westerman, H.C., undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Wexler, Allan & Ellen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Wexler, Allan & Ellen - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Wexler, Allan & Ellen - Reviews, undated (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Whiteford, Kate, undated (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Whiteford, Kate - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Whiteford, Kate - Reviews, undated (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Whiteford, Kate - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1992 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Whiteread, Rachel - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Whiteread, Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Whiteread, Rachel - Reviews, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Wides, Susan - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Wides, Susan - Photos/Slides, 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Wilding, Alison - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Wilding, Alison - Reviews, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Wilding, Alison - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Wilkie, Hannah - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Willenbecher, John, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Wilson, Fred - Reviews, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Wilson, Fred - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2006 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Wilson, Fred - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Wilson, Robert, undated (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Wilson, Robert - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Wilson, Robert - Photos/Slides, 1967-1993 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Wilson, Robert - Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Site (James Wines) - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1986-1996 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Site (James Wines) - Reviews, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Wines, James, undated (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Winsor, Jackie, undated (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Winter, David, undated (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Wintus, Robin, undated (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - Wischer, Wendy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Wischer, Wendy - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - Wischer, Wendy - Proposals, undated (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Wischer, Wendy, undated (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - Witkin, Issac, undated (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - Photos/Slides, 1988-1997 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1981-1987 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - Reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - Wolf, Silvio - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - Wolf, Silvio - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - Wolfe, James, undated (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - Wood, Steve, undated (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - Woodman, Betty and Sillman, Amy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Woodman, Betty and Sillman, Amy - Reviews, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Woodman, G., undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Woodman, Timothy, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Woodman, Timothy - Photos/Slides, 1993-1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Woodman, Timothy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Yagi, Mariyo - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Yagi, Mariyo - Reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Yamaguchi, Yoriko, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Yamamoto Lynn - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Yamamoto Lynn - Photos/Slides, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Yankowitz, Nina, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Yankowitz, Nina, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Yankowitz, Nina - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Yoder, Andy, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Young, Michael - Photos/Slides, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Youngblood, Daisy, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Youngblood, Daisy - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Younger, Robert, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Photos/Slides, 1976-1995 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Reviews, 1986, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Youngerman, Jack - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1985-2001 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Youngerman, Jack, 1977-1987 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Youngerman, Jack, 1977-1983 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Yuskavage, Lisa - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2004 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway - Reviews, 1994-1996 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway - Photos/Slides, 1987-1992 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway - Proposals, undated (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway, 1980-1990 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Zapkus, Kes, 1973-1995 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Zausner, Holly - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., undated (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Zhang, Hangtu, 1987, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Zhang, Jian-Jun - Photos/Slides, 2001-2005 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Zhang, Jian-Jun - Reviews, 2003-2005 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Zhang, Jian-Jun - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Zhang, Jian-Jun & Edelstein, Barbara, 1991-2004 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Zhen, Chen - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1996 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Zhen, Chen - Reviews, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Zimmerman, Edith, 1984-1995 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Zimmerman, Elyn - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1979-1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Zimmerman, Elyn - Photos/Slides, 1986-1994 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Zimmerman, Elyn - Reviews, 1975-1995 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Zimmerman, Elyn, 1978-1991 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Zittel, Andrea, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Zittel, Andrea - Photos/Slides, 1993-1997 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Zittel, Andrea - Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Zittel, Andrea - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1994-2007 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Zittel, Andrea - Proposals, undated (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Zlameeny/Insignia Esq Portrait Project: - Photos/Slides, undated (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Zlameeny/Insignia Esq Portrait Project: - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit info, Etc., undated (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Zlameeny/Insignia Esq Portrait Project: - Photos/Slides, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Zucker, Joe, undated (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Zwillinger, Rhonda, undated (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Zwillinger, Rhonda - Reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Zwillinger, Rhonda - Proposals, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Zwillinger, Rhonda - Invitations, Bio, Exhibit Info, Etc., 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Series II: Administrative Files
  Series II: Administrative Files includes Schwartz's professional correspondence, contracts, financial records, and project proposals. This series is arranged alphabetically by artist's last name, project title, or location.
  - 303 Gallery, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - [Airport], undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Airports, 1989, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Airports - Articles, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1994-2007 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - American Academy in Rome, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Elements Int./Ext. Art on Files, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Elements Int./Ext. Corp. Interiors, 1987-1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Architectural Elements Int./Ext. Floors-Ceilings, 1989-1995 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Architectural Elements Int./Ext. Lights, 1980-1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Architectural Elements Int./Ext. Stained Glass, 1981-1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Architectural Record, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Art Collection Maintenance, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Art Contracts, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Art Express, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - [Art General], undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Art in America: JPS Ad, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Art in America: 2 Public Art Review, 1983-1989 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Art - Miami, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Art Performance, 1981-1987 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Artist's Rights, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Artphile, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Arts for Transit, 1976, 1989, 1998-9 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Arts for Transit, 1985-1992 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Aycock JFK, 1998, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Barbara Mathes Gallery, undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Barcelona, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Battery Park - 1980's Art on the Beach, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Battery Park City, undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Battery Park City & Celle, undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Battery Park City Tour, undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Battery Park City Tour - Originals, undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Battery Park Correspondence, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Battery Park: Financial, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Battery Park Proposal - Robert Morris, undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Bellas Artes, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Berkshire Conf., undated (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Bills to pay, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Brochure: Color Copies, undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Brochure: Color Originals, undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Brochure Orig. 2003, undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Selected Originals for Brochures, undated (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Brochure: Original Color Copies, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 2004 Color Brochure Copies, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Brochure: Black and White Originals, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Camino Real, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - CD - Airports, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - CD - Stationary, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - CD - Wiley (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - CD ROM, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Central Florida Light Rail Transit, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Champs - Elysee Project, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Charles Ross Projects, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Charles Ross: Star Axis, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Charlotte NC: Exhibitions, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - China - Taiwan, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Cityscape Institute, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland: Artists & Architects Collaboration, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - "Cold call" Letters, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Collections: Private Collections, 1985-1997; 1985-1991 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Collectors, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Commissions: PACE, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Contract: Sample, 1976, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Samples, 1990, 1994, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - [Copenhagen Artifacts], 1986, 1994, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Copyright Issues, undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Copyrights, 1985, 1995, undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Art Articles, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Creative Time Coney Island, 2004-2005 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Cultural Planning, 1989-1990, 1992-1993; 1990 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Dai Ichi, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - David Saunders' Trout Project, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Documenta XI, undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - East Harlem Muralists, undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Encyclopedia of Architecture, Design, Engineering, & Construction - Vol. 4, undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Environmental Elements, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Elements - Gates and door, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Elements - Gazebos, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Elements - Play Spaces, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Elements - Signage (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Elements - Waterfronts, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Ideas, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Fabric Workshop, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Fabricators, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Fallingwater - Pittsburgh, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Fattoria di Celle - Four Seasons, 1985; 2003 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Florida Light Rail Transit, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Fountains, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Funding, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Gardens - Bellas Artes, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Germany: Art Sponsors, 1998, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Giuseppe Penone RDA, 1988, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Grand Rapids: Financial Contracts, 1995-1997 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Grand Rapids: Maya Lin, [2000] (Box 40, Folder 19)